# JONGHYUK (JOHN) LEE

# Full Stack Developer

#### CONTACT

jonghyuk82@gmail.com

(646)-577-4736

New York, NY 💿

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jongh yuk-john-lee-6bb6631a0

https://github.com/jonghyuk82

https://portfolio-one-iota-71.verce

l.app

#### **EDUCATION**

B.S.

Computer Science Queens College, CUNY January 2013 - December 2017 Queens, NY

#### SKILLS

C#(ASP.NET, ASP.NET Core, WPF)

Classic ASP

Javascript (ReactJS, jQuery)

TypeScript (Angular)

SignalR

SQL (MSSQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL,

NoSQL)

HTMI 5/CSS

Bootstrap

XUnit

**AWS** 

Azure DevOps

EDI

IBM MO

Git

Scrum/Agile

#### SUMMARY

Passionate software engineer with 5+ years of experience in developing web/desktop applications full-stack and practicing clean, concise code. Knowledgable in programming environments ranging from C# to JavaScript. Experienced working both small and large teams across multiple projects in an agile environment.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Software Engineer

Alinxsoft

March 2020 - current / New York, NY

- Contribute software engineering expertise on the development of payment portal applications for freight forwarders through SDLC, from requirement definition to successful deployments
- In charge of continuous development and management of EDI message parsing engines (software used by air cargo handling services)
- Work with core C# to develop automated solutions to include web interfaces using HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Proficiently troubleshoot issues requested from internal support teams, achieving high satisfaction rates

## Software Developer

The Notion Lab

February 2018 - March 2020 / New York, NY

- Developed new and maintained existing databases using a variety of technologies, languages and programming tools
- Worked on individual development projects to deliver secure, robust and scalable software that helped improve efficiency, information security, data integrity and customer satisfaction
- Designed and developed POS system solutions for over 50 clients using CSS, HTML, ASP.NET, and WPF

#### LANGUAGES

- English
- Korean